Here is a simple example,
这有一个简单的例子
where we generate features from text data using CountVectoriser
我们使用 CountVectoriser 和 TfidfTransformer 从文本数据中生成特征
and TfidfTransformer and then fit it to a RandomForestClassifier.
然后将其提供给 RandomForestClassifier
Let's use this to first go over
我们用这个来复习一些术语
some terminology and then learn how to use pipeline to simplify this.
然后学习如何使用管道来简化这个过程
Each of these three objects is called an estimator.
这三个对象都属于评估器 (estimator)
Which scikit-learn states, is any object that learns from data,
根据 scikit-learn 评估器是任何能够从数据中进行学习的对象
whether it's a classification,
无论它是一个
regression or clustering algorithm,
分类的、回归的、聚类的算法
or a transformer that extracts or filter is useful features from raw data.
或是从原始数据中提取或过滤有用信息的转换器 (transformer)
Because it learns from data,
因为它从数据中学习
every estimator must have a fit method that takes a dataset.
每个评估器都必须有一个 fit (拟合) 方法 接收一个数据集
So, each of these three estimators have a fit method.
所以 这三个评估器都有一个 fit 方法
Additionally, CountVectoriser and TfidfTransformer,
还有 CountVectoriser 和 TfidfTransformer
are a specific type of estimator called a transformer.
以及一类专门的评估器叫做转换器 (transformer)
Meaning it has a transform method.
意味着它有一个 transform (转换) 方法
The final estimator we have here is a predictor.
我们要介绍的最后一个评估器是预测器 (predictor)
Which although it doesn't have a transform method,
尽管预测器没有 transform 方法
has a predictor method.
但是它有一个 predict 方法
In machine learning tasks,
在机器学习任务中
it's pretty common to have a very specific sequence of
在经过最后一个评估器之前
transformers to fit to data before applying a final estimator.
经常会通过某些转换器的序列先拟合数据
Normally, we'd have to initialize all the estimators,
一般情况下 我们必须将所有评估器初始化
fit and transform the training data for each of
用每个转换器拟合数据 并转换训练数据
the transformers and then fit to the final estimator.
然后用最后的评估器拟合数据
Next, we'd have to call transform for each transformer again
接下来 我们必须再次调用转换器的 transform  转换测试数据
to the test data and finally call predict on the final estimator.
最后调用最后一个评估器的 predict
Now, what if I told you that you could actually automate all of this fitting,
现在 如果我告诉你其实可以将所有这些拟合 转换和预测
transforming and predicting by chaining
实现自动化
these estimators together into one single estimator object.
只需把这些评估器串联成一个评估器对象
That single estimator would be scikit-learns pipeline.
这一个评估器就是 scikit-learn 管道
To create this pipeline,
要创建这个管道
we just need a list of key value pairs.
我们只需要一个键值对的列表
Where the key is a string containing what you want to name
其中 键是字符串 表示你想要命名的步骤
the step and the value is the estimator object.
值是评估器对象
Now, by fitting our pipeline to the training data,
现在 通过管道拟合训练数据
we're accomplishing exactly what we would buy fitting and
我们可以实现用多个对象逐个拟合和转换训练数据
transforming each of these objects to our training data one by one.
一样的效果
Similarly, when we call predict on our pipeline to our test data,
类似的 当我们调用管道的 predict 方法来对测试数据进行预测时
we're accomplishing what we would by calling transform on each of
相当于每个转换器对象分别对测试数据调用 transform 方法
our transformer objects to our test data and then calling predict on our final estimator.
然后对最后一个评估器调用 predict 方法
Not only does this make our code is so much shorter and simpler,
不仅这种方法会让我们代码更加简洁
it has other great advantages which we'll cover in the next video.
另外的优点在下个视频中会提到
Note that every step of a pipeline has to be a transformer,
注意 管道中的每个步骤都必须是一个转换器
except for the last step,
除了最后一步之外
which can be an estimator of any type.
最后一步可以是任何类型的评估器
Pipeline takes on all the methods of whatever the last estimator in its sequence is.
管道的方法是由流程的最后一个评估器提供的
For example, here since the final estimator of our pipeline is a classifier,
例如 因为你的管道的最后一个评估器是分类器
the pipeline object can be used as a classifier.
管道对象可以被当做分类器使用
Taking on the fit and predict methods.
继承了 fit 和 predict 方法
Alternatively, if the last estimator was a transformer,
类似的 如果最后一个评估器是转换器
then pipeline would also be a transformer and you wouldn't be able to call predict on it.
管道对象可以当做转换器 你不能调用predict 方法